[{"answer": "my friend, all you want to do is come over here and get drunk", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Who? Me", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Did you try whistling", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Out where", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Please, can't you help me? I'm all alone", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He will call again! I know he will", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Tell you what. If this guy calls you again", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Okay, calm down now. I can alert the phone company so that if he calls again we can try to trace the call. What's your number there", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " I'm sorry I turned the lights down. It didn't work anyway. I can turn them back up if you like", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Don't?  You've really scared me. Is that what you wanted?  Is that what you wanted", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I know they haven't assigned anyone to it specifically. It's an old case", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes. Maybe not tomorrow, maybe not this week, but I'll find him", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend had it", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What is it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Okay now, what's the big deal", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "If you want me to remember something in the morning, then tell it to me in the morning", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Where're you from", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Sure. Sure I've been there", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " My name's my friend. I'm a private investigator", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " A private detective", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh, sure", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No, I don't believe you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " District Sales Manager", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Regional?", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Nothing's going on", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Operator", "docId": "When-a-Stranger-Calls.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " What is the number, please", "qsentId": 28}]